https://pacificvoiceware.com/privacy-statement/

Hit enter to search or ESC to close
Privacy StatementPacific VoiceWare Privacy Statement Pacific VoiceWare has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy.THIS IS OUR PRIVACY PROMISE TO YOU: Pacific VoiceWare/PacificVoiceWare.com will never sell, rent, or otherwise exchange, or release any of your individual personal information to a third party without your express permission. Pacific VoiceWare may, with your permission and ONLY with your permission, list your company name and/or web address on PacificVoiceWare.com in an effort to convey to perspective Pacific VoiceWare customers the quality of our work. This listing does not imply in any way your company’s endorsement or recommendation of Pacific VoiceWare or its services.INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT: It may be necessary for Pacific VoiceWare to collect names, telephone numbers, email addresses and/or your company’s physical address in order to deliver our services. Pacific VoiceWare/PacificVoiceWare.com will never sell, exchange, or release any of this information to a third party without your express permissionCOOKIES Like many sites, Pacific VoiceWare uses cookies to track and record your preferences and activity on our website. Cookies are small bits of data that are sent to your browser and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information. Each time you access our site, our server may deliver certain customized information to you based on the data stored in your cookie. We also collect IP addresses for system administration and to track aggregate information.Some Web sites that have links on our site may also use their own cookies.If you do not wish to accept cookies, your browser software should allow you to disable cookies. Look in the Preferences or Internet Options feature to do this. This will not have any effect on what is displayed to you while visiting PacificVoiceWare.com.LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES PacificVoiceWare.com may contain links to other sites. Pacific VoiceWare is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. PacificVoiceWare.com does not share any of the individual personal information you provide PacificVoiceWare.com with the sites to which PacificVoiceWare.com links, although PacificVoiceWare.com may share aggregate data with such sites such as how many people visit our site.Please check with those sites to determine their privacy policy.CONTACTING PACIFIC VOICEWARE If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of Pacific VoiceWare or the PacificVoiceWare.com site, please contact:PacificVoiceWare PO Box 1663 Bastrop, TX 78602
HomeSamplesClientsPricesDeliveryPrivacy StatementTerms of Use Pacific Voiceware PO BOX 1663 Bastrop, TX 78602888.678.8642PacificVoiceWare@Gmail.com Copyright © 1998-2020 Pacific VoiceWare. All Rights Reserved.Kauai, Hawaii Photos by Joe Westerberg
Let Our Voices Work for YouHomeSamplesClientsPricesDeliveryContact
